I'm so deeply disturbed. Just watch, just.
The collective punishment, as he put it, of the Palestinian people.
And I want to talk about that in the context of the blockade and keeping fuel out of Gaza.
I just wonder if you think that that is really necessary.
You know, I'm very puzzled by the constant concern which the world and also Britain, I must say, Mark,
is showing for the Palestinian people and is actually showing for these horrible, inhuman animals
who have done the worst atrocities that this century has seen.
So it went from Hamas to now, why is there concern for the Palestinian people?
Are y'all not, this is, this, I'm utterly speechless.
I'm terrified at the moral apathy, the death of the heart, which is happening in my country.
These people have deluded themselves for so long that they really don't think I'm human.
I admit this on their conduct, not on what they say.
And this means that they have become, in themselves, moral monsters.